I was at an event at the weekend called
Clean Health Live.
Clean Health pretty much help personal
trainers get qualified, and they run
educational courses. They're online.
And I was a guest speaker.
I got asked a question on a panel,
and to be honest, I didn't even know I was
supposed to be on this panel. It
was just lucky that I
was outside the room when it
went on. And this is what Hayley said.
I'm a mum of three, and I work seven days.
And I start at 5:30, work at the gym,
come home, and then I work
till 7:00 doing my own business.
My question is, how do you know when
to stop a safe, secure income for
your own business?
So quickly here,
the second I heard this question,
I appreciate that a lot of
people are in the world of a safety net.
They're employed. They're earning money.
They have a side quest or a venture
that they want to get into,
and there has to be
a moment of taking a leap. Now,
the second I heard this, I
was in a similar place,
but my leap was going from in-person PT to
fully going online.
And I'm in Fitness First,
and one detail I keep out the videos
is I never got
above six clients in Sydney. So in the UK,
I was fully booked
for years, and there
were five coaches at the gym.
I was probably number one
or the number two biggest earner there.
When I arrived in Sydney, there
was 32 personal trainers in the gym.
I was there for a year. My rent
was $400 a week, so about £200.
And about 10 of those personal trainers I
never even spoke to for the duration of
the year.
It was a pretty hostile environment,
and I've told a lot of people that
someone tried to fight me on my first day
at work.
So I thought I would answer her question
with this.
You're going to be in a position where
if you don't make it work, you are
fucked.
And I cannot express to you how magical
that is for
progress.
So rather than being fearful of the
desperation and sticky
position you put yourself in,
you're not going to believe me until it
happens, but
a year from now,
you'll be so grateful
that you exposed yourself to this
because there is a certain level
that you're going to find that
you can only find if you commit.
So just before I told her this, I
mentioned there's a story. So I
was personal training in George Street
Fitness
First, and I'd get to work, well,
6:00 a.m.
because that's where the gym
was the busiest.
But before then,
I had to do a live on Facebook.
So I would have to probably start
that live at about quarter past 5:00 in
the
morning. Now, I could do
that live at home,
but my housemates would kill me.
So I used to get up, I think about 4:30.
I used to chuck my personal training kit
on.
I used to walk from Bondi Junction to the
train station, get the train into the
city, get off at Martin Place,
and there was a food court called
Australia Square.
And some people remember this, but it
was so early in the morning
that they had the
little sweepers where they're polishing
the floors.
And I'd get out my tripod,
and I'd go live because I knew
that every day I had to
do a live stream,
and I had to be in the gym at 6:00.
So 5:15 it was.
And online, I had a handful of clients,
but my face-to-face business was really
tough.
And because of the hostility of the gym,
I didn't know it at the time, but I
had this big internal dilemma where
although I was trying to build a business,
I
actually didn't want to build a business
because I didn't like it there.
There were no windows. It was dark.
I didn't really have any friends.
The only trainer there
that had really spoken to me was Darren,
and he introduced
me to his mate, James,
who I now own James Smith Academy with.
And there's a moment, it was March 13th,
2017.
I remember it clear as day.
I've still got screenshots of it.
I'm in a group chat with my two
housemates, gorgeous George
and Ben Willets.
Still good friends to this day.
And there was a group chat we had called
1522.
That was our address. And we used to say,
"It's not a location.
It's a way of life." And they went, "Oi,
Smithy, how's it going?" And I'll never
forget, I sat there in Australia Square,
kind of on my laptop, thinking.
I was like,
"How do I answer this question?"
And I had to answer them and say, "Not
good." I prospected all morning.
I had no consults booked in.
I had no leads.
I only had one PT session for the day.
My rent wasn't even getting covered by the
amount of sessions I was doing.
I was losing money, and I
was not earning enough online.
And it was only when I typed "not good"
into that WhatsApp bar that I
realized my situation.
I kind of knew up here it wasn't good,
but the second I
typed it, I was like,
"Oh." Started thinking about the
repercussions.
If I can't afford my rent here,
I can't just go into another gym because
then I'm
going to be paying rent in two places.
Not to mention,
I'm already struggling enough with the
rent in the apartment.
Then there's the fact
that about three weeks before, George
and Ben went to IKEA,
kitted out the flat, came back, and went,
"You owe us $600." About £300.
I said, "What do you mean?" They're like,
"Oh, we bought the cutlery.
We've got the bowls. We've got the plates.
We got this. We got that.
We got outdoor furniture."
And I remember at this point,
I had to go to my dad and
say, "Dad,
can I borrow 300 quid?" I'm 27 at this
point. And he emailed me.
He sent me the money, and he said,
"Don't tell your mum." Because he knew my
mum
would get worried if she knew I had
monetary problems.
So I'll never forget kind of sitting there
looking at that, "not good." I was like,
"I need to do something about this."
And instead of going back to the gym,
I turned
around and went in the other direction.
I went to a shop
that we have in Australia called
Officeworks.
I got myself a static whiteboard,
stick on the wall,
got myself some marker pens,
got myself a tripod
that would hold an iPhone in it.
And on the walk home,
I put in a podcast to an evidence-based
pod,
and I would learn about one topic.
And I'd listen to it for about 45 minutes,
get
in front of my phone, and I'd be like,
"Okay, five, four, three." Hit
record. Go live.
Because I didn't know how to edit.
I didn't have a camera.
[chuckles] My laptop couldn't edit.
I didn't know how to edit.
I didn't understand any of this.
And I had to perform for 10 to 12 minutes
on that
live stream, then upload,
and hope for the best.
But it was that day
that I realized I had to give up on my
dream of being an
in-person PT,
and I had to make it work online.
And if I didn't do that,
I had to move back home into my parents'
house, and I had
to go back to the gym that I just left.
So imagine being in a gym for three
and a half years, being the top dog.
"I'm going to Australia.
Going to live a better life."
And then being back six
months later, tail between your leg.
"I ran out of money,
and I couldn't make it work." So what I
was saying there, I
was trying to portray to Hayley
that you kind of need that desperation.
If I look back to any kind of time in my
life I've done really well, there's been a
precursor of desperation.
Then whilst the other people are speaking,
I can't stop
thinking.
I spent about five minutes about Hayley's
situation, and I was like,
"She's got kids. She's got a mortgage.
She's got a partner.
Spending all day at the gym." It wasn't
even the financial side of things I
thought
about. It was how I would feel
if I had to work and I couldn't see my
son.
That's just one kid, not three.
And then next to me as well, I've got
Adam Sullivan, personal trainer.
Used to hate him. Another video.
One of my really good friends now.
And I've kind of witnessed him be very
generous,
let's just say. And
if I look at him carefully,
I don't think he's being generous
so much always for the other person.
He's doing it for himself because it makes
him feel better.
Friday night, he was like,
"Let's go get some cash
and give it to homeless people."
He wasn't like,
"Go get a camera." It wasn't like,
"Go get a phone." He was like,
"Let's get some cash.
Let's go give it to homeless people."
And I was like, "What a
way to get a kick." [chuckles] You know?
So I'm sat there, and I'm like,
"Give me the mic back." And this
is what I said.
Sorry, what was your name,
the lady who wanted to quit her job?
Hayley.
Sorry, I've been thinking about this.
If you quit next week,
I will personally financially guarantee
that you will
not be out of pocket. So
if you quit the gym,
we'll give you six months.
If at any point you're in a financial
deficit, I'll cover it.
I will work with you personally-
[clapping]
Let's go
... to grow your business one-to-one,
and then we get to use case
your transformation so
that we can help other women do it.
Sorry, Claire, keep quiet.
Oh, that's just too good.
Love it.
If James doesn't get you, I will.
Oh.
Hit me up.
This is like "Shark Tank" now.
So for me, there is one annoying thing.
It's a comment from LinkedIn, and
that comment says this, "James,
that's not really
helping her.
That's giving her a safety net,
and safety nets stop people from ever
going all in.
Real success only comes from
when you burn the boats.
A mentor covering her losses might feel
supportive, but I'm not sure it gives her
the mindset she actually needs."
And he's welcome to his opinion,
but I'm going to
prove you why this is wrong.
Because firstly,
I'll get this off my chest.
You want to know the number one reason I'm
doing this?
And it's going to sound really bad.
To make me feel better.
I made more money than I've ever made in
my life last month, and it was cool, but
the reaction that not only I got from
Hayley, but Hayley's partner, was
better.
Her partner took me aside about an hour
later, and he pretty much just said
to me, "She's working so hard
that she's on the verge of not being able
to do this
anymore." And I said to him,
"Here's my email address.
If she doesn't hit me up on the offer,
I'll come to you direct
and we'll sort this
out." So firstly, this
is a selfish gesture.
I said this to Hayley too.
I go,
"Me doing this will make me feel better
than half the other stuff."
Because at that point in my life,
I only had my dad, and I
was very fortunate that
my dad had £300 that he could give me to
help me buy a fridge.
And there have been so many moments in my
life where I've not had someone like
that.
Even young Declan outside doing this edit,
if he comes into financial
hardship, I can take care of him.
Going to have to pay me back.
He'll be editing for me until he's 50,
but he'll still have to pay me back, but
still.
And I kind of know the exact issue
that Hayley's in.
But the reason number two I'm doing this
isn't for Hayley, it's for all the
Hayleys. It's for the thousands of people,
male and female, with families,
without families,
who have got one foot in a business
and one foot in ambition.
Now, for me, I can accept people failing,
but I can't accept people staying in this
situation.
Going to get in some of it a bit now so
that everyone can kind of
understand the dire situation of remaining
in this.
Now,
I'm not going to disclose too much of the
personal stuff that Hayley sent to
me.
And I will be visiting her probably in the
next month.
Declan and I will fly down. We will,
first of all,
help her film some content where
she is, give her some feedback,
and we'll keep checking in with her.
It's in my best interest because the
better she does, the less it costs me.
You know what I mean? So, we get
that business up and running,
I'll be sending her
the odd dollar here and there.
Got to get my investment back.
Okay,
let's look at the pitfall of remaining
employed when running a business.
For that, we best go downstairs.
A little side note, NuTONIC,
if you haven't tried
it already, you're dead to me. God yeah.
Was yours a bit icy? It's good, that.
So unfortunately for Hayley,
she's having to work a full week at work
and
then do her personal training on top of
that.
There's a lot of personal trainers
that do this.
So let's go Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday,
Thursday,
Friday, Saturday, Sunday. Go 6:00 AM,
7:00 AM, 8:00,
9:00, 10:00. So at the moment,
that part of Hayley's week
pretty much belongs to the gym.
So she's now having to build her business
on the
outside of that. So let's imagine
that she's having Sundays off,
which I don't
think she is. These hours here
are going to be the personal training
sessions that
she can do. The annoying belief is
that a lot of people think for a personal
trainer, that these are your bread
and butter sessions.
But I may remind you that from,
let's say 5:00, 6:00, 7:00 PM, this is
an awful time to be a personal trainer
because something like a bench press is
a piece of equipment
that a lot of people want.
So when I used to train people in the
evenings, don't know if this
is same for you,
someone's paying you a good amount of
money, and you're like, "Oh, the bit of
equipment we need has got two people on
it." And you kind of just got to stand
around with your client and be like,
"So how was your weekend?"
And 10 minutes of the session's gone,
you got one set of
bench press out. As a personal trainer,
you do not want to have your diary full
during the busy times of the day.
You want it during the quiet times,
and the way
you can do that is through marketing.
But anyway.
Now, Hayley's biggest problem
is the same problem
that a lot of you youngsters are
going to face if you don't fix
and sort your PT business
and drive demand for your
services. For me, growing up,
my dad would leave the house at 7:00 AM
because he
had to drive to the train station,
park at the train station,
get the train into
London. That took an hour. Swap trains,
get into the City of London, then do the
same on the way back.
I wouldn't see him until 7:00 PM.
And I don't agree with this,
but he said to me he wished he
was around more for my
childhood. But growing up,
I don't ever think
that my dad wasn't there.
But anyway,
that's one of his insecurities as an older
person.
Now,
when looking at Hayley's existing
situation, she doesn't
get to see her children at all.
She's got three kids.
Because she gets up,
she works for the gym all day.
The kids come home from school,
and she won't mind me saying this,
the kids then go
to her mom's house.
And then by the time
that she's finished PT in the evening, her
kids are in bed already asleep,
and she won't see them again until
potentially the
school run,
if she can have a bit of time off from the
gym to go get her kids and
drop them home. This may pay the bills,
but it's not congruent with a good life,
nor an acceptable life. Now,
we won't use exact figures,
but let's say that the
gym pays her $1,200 a week, and that
is for 39 hours of
work. That works out to circa $30 an hour.
Don't check my maths.
So what I've said is
that I'm going to replace this
straightaway.
And this is actually the second time I've
done this.
I have a member of staff who
was working in PureGym, and his rent in
PureGym was £800 a month,
but they only wanted him to work 12 hours
a week.
So I said to him, "Hey,
why don't I pay your gym rent for you
and you work for me
12 hours a week?
And then you can learn from me,
learn the trade, whatever it is."
Because this time on the gym floor working
for the gym I think is
dead counterintuitive and not productive.
First of all,
it's going to be difficult to command a
good hourly rate over here if
you're here wiping down leg presses
and changing toilet paper in the
toilets. Now, the worst part
is these hours for $30
an hour have to stay at $30 an hour.
So using this maths, here's what I want to
propose. And for anyone out there, this
is Australian dollars, so
half it for Great British pounds.
And some people are going to turn their
nose up,
go, "£600 a week,
that's loads." Not the purpose of the
video.
First thing,
each PT rate going to be set at $60.
So that's £30 an hour.
There's nothing we're going to do to
change that.
But the beauty of this
is I take over all the risk inside here.
Now,
I've just given back Hayley 39 hours a
week.
First thing I said to her was,
"Have a lay-in,
go spend some time with your kids."
Because the first thing
that I want to do is I want actually
Hayley to start
sleeping in till 8:00
or 9:00 AM every morning, or even 7:00 AM,
not doing any
work. Go hang with her kids for a bit.
Drop the kids to school.
So let's say that's 9:00. And Hayley,
if you're watching this, which I hope you
are, I want you to do this. Even
if it takes us twice as long to get to
this
earning point,
I just want you to spend a bit of time
with your kids.
I want you to wake up, have some toast,
have a cup of coffee.
Let your kids wake you up, whatever it is.
I want you to get energy back from this
part to begin with.
If I catch you waking up at 6:00 AM,
I will not be happy.
And again,
I'm happy to keep paying this for as long
as it takes.
All I ask is that you help us document it
so we can help other women.
Which you seem sound.
You'll do this anyway.
Now, this part of your afternoon,
I want us to focus on building your
business.
Now, another thing I want us to do
is to chill from this bit onwards.
The reason I want us to chill here
is because I want that time.
You're about to do evening PT sessions.
Also,
your kids are going to come home from
school.
I want you to pick them up,
bring them home,
chill with them for a bit.
So this is going to become lifestyle time.
Now,
the times I want you to focus on building
your business, between 9:00 AM
and 2:00 PM. If someone says, "Hey,
I want to do a session at 5:00 or at 4:00
Say, "Sorry,
I'm just not training people at
that time." Now, all we need to figure
out is how many PT sessions a week do we
need to do at $60 to
earn $1,200. 60 times 20. Yeah.
For us to meet this amount, Haley needs to
do 20 PT sessions a week.
So even at the introductory rate,
$60, if she never climbs above that,
she's already
19 hours better off a week.
So just taking her from working for the
gym to running her own PT sessions,
she can do half the hours at double the
money.
She gets 19 hours back to spend with her
kids, her family, and better yet,
to work on her business.
But her price will only really ever go up
due to building
demand and inflation,
mostly through building demand.
The second thing we need to consider
is this money that she earns is something
called PAYE.
Could be something different in Australia.
It's pretty much income from a business,
which means that it can make it, for a
lot of you pure gym-ers,
a lot more difficult to utilize
that better from a tax
perspective.
When you earn the money from personal
training, it goes into a
business account.
Then you can spend things
that you need for the business, like a
MacBook or a phone,
or you might even get a certain amount of
your Wi-Fi back, or
your telecommunication data, whatever,
because that would actually be a
legitimate
business cost.
When you're employed for a gym,
I know in the UK, for example,
it's a lot more difficult to claim
expenses through that.
So even if she was to earn the exact same
money personal training versus working
for the gym, she saves 19 hours,
probably going to get some more tax
benefits writing things off through her
own business, reducing profitability.
Again, this is not a tax video. So
if she needs 20 hours, one, two,
three, four, five.
Let's say we don't want her working
Saturdays either. Why? Because kids.
Suddenly, all we're looking at
is four PT sessions a day. That's alright,
isn't it?
Four times five is 20. Perfect.
So on Monday, she might do one PT session,
two PT sessions,
take a little bit of a break,
then come in for the afternoon.
Maybe on Tuesday, she comes in,
she does three with a little break,
then one more.
Then unfortunately,
she has to do one there. Fine.
Then on Wednesday,
she just does four in a row,
then she gets a little bit of an
afternoon off. Thursday,
two in the morning, two in the afternoon.
Friday, one, then she has three in a row.
Suddenly,
Haley's still getting lunch breaks.
She's still getting a bit of time off.
If there is an annoying just one hour
between clients,
I would say to her go to a
local cafe, get your laptop out.
Let's maybe write some LinkedIn posts,
or let's
schedule and script some videos
or whatever it is.
During this, maybe we walk the floor.
Maybe here, we talk to our clients
and ask them for some testimonials.
Maybe here,
she can study in the business mentorship
that I've given her free
access to. Now,
I want this time here to be with the kids.
However,
when she picks the kids up from school,
I don't mind if she then comes
home and makes a bit of content,
gets the tripod out, does some videos.
I don't even mind if she gets the kids
involved in the content, having a bit of
fun, spending some time with them.
Because Haley's a mom of three,
she's going to find it super relatable to
give
advice to other moms of three. Obviously,
you don't want to put kids on social
media if you don't want.
But another thing that I would say is
if Haley wants to
conduct personal training sessions from
her home because she's got a home gym, I
would do some flyering.
I would get some flyers made,
and I'd give them out.
And this is where some people, I think,
can make a bit of a mistake.
Rather than that flyer saying,
"My name's Haley,
I'm a personal trainer." I would
even maybe go out with your kids
if they're old enough, especially
if you've got,
like, a 15-year-old boy. Say,
"I hope you don't mind my son put this
through your
letterbox. My name's Haley.
I live in Yarra Valley." Sometimes even
say to people
to put your road, because
if you're going to put flyers out to the
local area and
you're like, "Yeah,
we're on Fenchurch Street." "I know
Fenchurch Street.
My nan used to live on
that street." You already feel like you
know each other.
Similar to, like, when you go on holiday,
someone's like, "Where do you live?"
You're like, "Oh,
I live in Wollongong." "No way.
We live in Wollongong." "Bro,
he lives in Wollongong.
Can you believe it?" So already, this
is her potential life.
Way better off, same money,
if not potentially more.
Then there are two ways
which we would probably move up from here.
The one thing I would say is 20
is the amount she needs to break even.
The ceiling, I would say,
is probably 25 to 30.
So let's just put this here.
The maximum amount of sessions,
I think Haley should be 25.
I would say for most people
that don't have kids
or family commitments, it'd be 30.
And I would actually be completely fine
if Haley never did more than 20.
Now, once she gets full,
I would probably ask her to start dropping
the evening
sessions,
and I'd rather this part came across to
the afternoon.
The only reason I'm keeping this here for
the time being is that she already has
clients in the evening.
She's already doing those.
But as time fills up, I would see
if we can migrate these people.
Even if it was just three days a week
that they would come in, and we get some
evenings back.
So then she's only working late three
nights a week.
And even now,
she would come to the gym at 9:00 a.m.
She could go home for a bit between 10:00
and 12:00, come in for the afternoon
shift. She gets to go home at 6:00.
This is already looking a lot better.
Once she's hit this maximum amount of
sessions,
there's only one thing you can do,
and that's put your rates up. Now,
if she's charging $60 an hour,
it would be real
chilled. It'd be like $60 to $65. Now,
some people say, "Oh, do you put
everyone's rates up?" In a perfect world,
yes.
But if you want to grandfather any people
in on the old rate because they're a
legend, you can. Jackie Smith,
Susan Green, two clients that I had
that were just such OGs
that I never put their rates up.
Now, $5 can seem like a trivial amount,
but five times 20
is every time that Haley puts her rates up
by $5, she's got
$100 more in the pocket. Now,
for some of you out there, you might go,
"What if a
couple people drop off?" Well,
if she loses one client because of the
price
increase, she's still up $40
and doing one hour less.
People are really scared to increase the
hourly rate, but if you're doing it
through demand, it's fine. And
if people want to challenge you for why
you're
putting your rates up,
you just say the one thing you need to
say.
"Sorry,
I'm getting too busy." Because the one
thing that we cannot go back
into is spending all day,
every day at the gym.
The thing that I need to help Haley do
is to get these training sessions,
and the way we're going to do that
is by building demand.
The way we're going to build demand,
two ways. And for that, we'll go upstairs.
Now, the first thing that I would say
is this.
I would love people to have online
businesses.
That's what my mentorships are about,
helping people make money online.
But the reality is this.
For those of you with an in-person trade,
it is so much
faster to get someone to start doing
business with you in person.
For instance, today,
I could walk the floor,
have a conversation with someone, say,
"Hey,
I'm looking to be a bit more priced on the
gym floor.
Can I give you a free introductory session
tomorrow?
It'll be from 10:00 to 11:00 because
that's the time you came in today.
There's absolutely no obligation to train
with me.
I just want to show you what I can do."
They go, "Yeah, okay, cool." Tomorrow,
they
come in. I train them from 10:00 to 11:00.
We go through different movement patterns.
We look at the squat, we look at the RDL.
Maybe I say, "Oh, do you know what?
I think you're doing this incorrectly." I
help them a little bit.
They go, "Wow,
never felt this before." Talk to them a
little bit about their
goals, what they're struggling to do,
what they maybe want to do.
And at the end, you go, "Look,
I actually think you know what you're
doing.
What I propose is
that I write you a program.
It has four sessions in per week.
I would like to be present for one of
those sessions.
Typically, I would charge this per hour.
But how about this?
For this hourly rate,
you get all four workouts.
Every Monday,
we go through how you got on,
what you're looking towards.
We'll go through your measurements,
et cetera, whatever,
and it's going to cost
this amount. I propose
that you pay for 12 weeks.
You can do it half now or all upfront,
completely up to you.
And if we don't get the results
that you want or you seek the progressions
you tell
me are important,
I'll refund you in full." Boom.
They pay within 24 hours, 48 hours,
you've got a client.
That does not happen online. Takes months.
Even some of you guys watching this,
you might have to watch my content for
five,
six,
seven hours before you even go through to
the landing page.
You might have to read my emails for a few
weeks.
Even the link in this description for "30
Ways in 30 Days," the average person
reads those for 19 days in a row before
buying.
So we must have an in-person strategy
first.
That's why to Hayley,
the first thing I'm going to say to her
is, "Let's try
flyering." I do hope that actually,
even the way we're working together doing
this video,
anyone in Yarra Valley in Melbourne could
reach out to her and start
working with her.
I want to start building the socials,
creating some content.
I want to start building her email list.
But the truth is, building socials
and an email list is a three-
to six-month task.
We're not going to see the fruition of
that for months.
The in-person thing
is the thing we need to do straight away.
And actually, what I need Hayley to do
is some of the ugly stuff, flyering,
walking
the floor, asking for referrals.
And for that, she needs time.
She cannot do that
while she's employed by the gym.
That's why I've taken that over for her.
The other important thing is,
that business owners don't talk about
enough, is
protecting your energy.
The reason I want Hayley to start having
some lay-ins is
because building an online brand,
you get beaten up a lot.
You get to eat shit a lot.
When she's walking that floor
and people are saying,
"I'm not interested,"
when she's going out there
and she's not getting the
responses she wants, I at least know
that she got a good night's sleep the
night
before. I at least know
that she's going to pick up the kids from
school and get to
spend a bit of time with them.
If you don't get those bits of recharging
in
between,
you're going to find this a lot harder
than you need to.
For so many people out there that
are considering making the leap,
I appreciate
that it's going to be more difficult
when you have kids
and you have other things
involved,
but you just need to ask yourself this,
and this is a pretty difficult
and pressing thing to do.
How much work do I need to do to be better
off?
That's the question. For Hayley,
20 PT sessions, undercharging.
$60 an hour. It's £30.
It's less than what it
was 15 years ago for a PT session.
20 hours doing that versus 39
and a half hours for the gym.
It's a no-brainer.
Then the beautiful thing is,
because I suspect where Hayley lives
is a bit more
remote,
and that can be an influencing factor in
your hourly rate.
When we start to build things up online,
we could easily get her to, let's say,
$100 a week. And
that $100 a week means you get all your
programs, you get a
check-in, you get someone to talk to,
and then she would only need 12 clients to
be
better off.
12 clients isn't a lot of people.
If I said to Hayley,
"Would you rather do 39 hours a week in
the gym or manage
12 clients online?" It's a no-brainer.
Best thing about working online as well,
even for myself, the reason that I don't
do calls anymore is because my day can be
hectic.
So I've got a Discord full of people right
in front of me here that I'm looking at.
I'm going to open my laptop,
and I'm going to deal with them
when I can, and I'm
going to close my laptop, and I'm not
when I can't.
That's the main freedom of working online
and operating your own business, is you
get to determine
when you give your clients your time
and energy.
Rather than it being an hour on a
Wednesday at 11:00 a.m.,
you get to open it, and
you can even just say to people, "Hey,
I had a really busy day.
I'll be back in tomorrow." Over the next
coming weeks and months, what I want to
find out is how long it takes us for
Hayley to get to that point of break even
and above it.
And then I want to go ask her herself how
hard it was.
Because if a lady in remote Melbourne can
do it in
12 weeks with three kids, I think
that could be quite an inspiring story for
other
people,
and I'm going to be keeping you up to date
on it.
So I'm going to put a link to Hayley's
Instagram.
On Instagram,
she's down as Yarra Valley Performance.
Although, I want to change
that immediately to Hayley Dubouf.
So stay tuned.
We're going to blow Hayley up.
And all I want in return from you lot
is to do the
quiz that I've put in the description
below.
If you do that,
it'll tell you where you need to focus on
your business. All right.
About time I check in with Hayley.
Speak to you in a bit. Bye-bye.